I originally thought I could get both cash and goods.
처음에는 현금과 물품을 모두 받을 수 있다고 생각했어요.
I thought it was quite beautiful
꽤 예쁘다고 생각했는데
I don’t want to provoke the devil Yamashita either.
나도 악마 야마시타를 자극하고 싶지 않다.
Why don't you tell me not to give him the formula?
그에게 공식을 주지 말라고 나한테 말해보는 게 어때?
OK
좋아요
It seems you really didn't lie to me
당신은 정말 나에게 거짓말을 하지 않은 것 같아요
Why did I lie to you?
내가 왜 당신에게 거짓말을 했나요?
We two brothers
우리 두 형제
We'll be there soon
곧 도착할 거예요
I'll give you two more big yellow croakers
큰 민어 두 마리 더 드릴게요
Half an hour passed
30분이 지났다
I haven't gone to the Gendarmerie Headquarters yet.
나는 아직 헌병대 본부에 가지 않았습니다.
Uchida must doubt me
우치다는 나를 의심해야 해
Be gentle, Mrs. Luo
부드럽게 대해주세요, 루오 부인
The sound insulation here is not good
여기 방음이 잘 안되네요
large spoon
큰 숟가락
This is no place for people to stay.
이곳은 사람이 머물 곳이 아니다.
Just make do with it
그냥 해내세요
Come
오다
Mrs. Luo
루오 부인
You sit over there
당신은 거기 앉아
It seems the recipe
레시피인 것 같아요
It has fallen into Zhang Shuyun's hands
장수윤의 손에 넘어갔다
If Luo Guanqun is allowed to meet her,
Luo Guanqun이 그녀를 만나는 것이 허용된다면
There will be no chance again
다시는 기회가 없을 거예요
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
didn't you see
못 봤어?
Two figures ran over
두 인물이 뛰어 넘었다
silhouette
실루엣
Have it
그것을 가지고
Who is it?
누구입니까?
He can't be a Japanese spy, right?
그 사람은 일본 스파이가 될 수 없잖아요?
Is it safe for you to find that place?
그 곳을 찾는 것이 안전한가요?
Of course it's safe
물론 안전해요
You read that right?
그거 읽은 거 맞지?
No
아니요
cannot
할 수 없다
Big brother
형
you wait here
여기서 기다리세요
I'll go check it out for you
내가 가서 확인해 볼게
Give me the gun
총을 줘
good
좋은
If there's a problem I'll shoot
문제 있으면 쏘겠습니다
When you hear gunshots, drive away immediately.
총소리가 들리면 즉시 차를 몰고 떠나세요.
Be careful
조심하세요
good
좋은
Understood
이해했다
I went
나는 갔다
Who is it?
누구입니까?
It should be Lao Luo who has arrived.
도착한 사람은 Lao Luo 여야합니다.
How could it be so fast?
어떻게 그렇게 빠를 수 있었나요?
Who?
WHO?
who
WHO
broken
고장난
I'm late
나는 늦었다
The formula must have been taken away by the Japanese
공식은 일본이 빼앗아 갔을 것입니다
How about it
어때요?
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
too nervous
너무 긴장하다
I read it wrong
내가 잘못 읽었어
That's good
좋아요
Lao Luo
라오루오
Just walk in
그냥 들어가세요
You won’t send me as a gift
넌 나한테 선물로 보내지 않을 거야
The road there is too narrow
거기 길이 너무 좁아요
It's hard to drive the car out when it's in
차가 들어가면 나가기가 힘들다.
Besides, Zuo Shuangtao and I also have to run for our lives.
게다가 저와 Zuo Shuangtao도 목숨을 걸고 달려야 합니다.
Leave the gun for me for self-defense
정당방위를 위해 총은 나에게 맡겨두세요
Do you still have some there?
거기 아직도 좀 갖고 있나요?
OK
좋아요
bullion
지금
I'll come back to you tomorrow to get it.
내일 다시 찾아오겠습니다.
Aren't you afraid that I'll run away?
내가 도망갈까 두렵지 않아?
If you can escape
탈출할 수 있다면
hide here
여기에 숨어
OK
좋아요
Be careful
조심하세요
Lao Luo
라오루오
There's something else
뭔가 다른 게 있어요
I've been following you for so long
나는 오랫동안 당신을 따라왔습니다.
We parted ways immediately
우리는 즉시 헤어졌다
What kind of person am I in your eyes?
당신의 눈에 나는 어떤 사람인가요?
It's hard to say
말하기 어렵다
I have to think about it
생각해봐야 해
I'll tell you tomorrow
내일 말해줄게
Go tomorrow
내일 가세요
talk tommorow
내일 얘기해
I'll send you here
여기로 보내드릴게요
Who?
WHO?
I
나
Open the door quickly
빨리 문을 열어라
Lao Luo
라오루오
Don't blame me
나를 비난하지 마세요
There's nothing I can do
내가 할 수 있는 일은 아무것도 없어
I originally thought it was because of what happened last time
원래는 지난번 일 때문인 줄 알았는데
you haven't forgiven me yet
당신은 아직 나를 용서하지 않았습니다
Will he find another woman?
그 사람은 다른 여자를 찾을 수 있을까요?
So I'll follow you all the way
그러니 난 당신을 끝까지 따라갈 거예요
Followed all the way to the phone booth on Sanguantang Road
Sanguantang Road에 있는 전화부스까지 따라갔습니다.
I saw you take out that precious colorful phoenix tail pen
그 귀하고 알록달록한 봉황꼬리 펜을 꺼내는 걸 봤어
take something out of it
그것에서 뭔가를 꺼내
Put it behind the phone
전화기 뒤에 놓으세요.
I don't know what you want to do
당신이 무엇을 하고 싶은지 모르겠어요
After you leave
당신이 떠난 후
I'll take away what you hid
네가 숨긴 걸 내가 가져갈게
When I got home, I studied for a long time
집에 돌아와서 오랫동안 공부했어요
I can’t even figure out what it is.
나는 그것이 무엇인지조차 알 수 없습니다.
So I didn’t pay too much attention to it.
그래서 나는 그것에 별로 관심을 기울이지 않았다.
But until tonight
하지만 오늘 밤까지
I only found out after hearing your conversation with Chen Jiaping
Chen Jiaping과의 대화를 듣고서야 알았습니다.
what you hide
당신이 숨기는 것
It turned out to be Chief Uchida
우치다 대장으로 밝혀졌습니다
what they've been looking for
그들이 무엇을 찾고 있었는지
Now you have to take me and run away
이제 나를 데리고 도망쳐야 해
I just want
난 그냥 원해요
Why can't you men move?
너희들은 왜 움직일 수 없느냐?
I just want to run away with a woman
그냥 여자랑 도망가고 싶어
Do you think I will be touched?
내가 감동받을 것 같아?
Have you asked me about my wishes?
내 소원을 물어본 적 있나요?
I don't want to run
나는 달리고 싶지 않다
Anyone take me to run
누구든지 나를 달리게 해주세요
I won't even run
난 도망치지도 않을 거야
so
그래서
The way you asked Damasau to take me here
당신이 다마사우에게 나를 여기로 데려가달라고 부탁한 것처럼
It's Chief Uchida I called.
내가 전화한 사람은 우치다 과장이다.
and gave the thing to him
그리고 그에게 그 물건을 주었다
Chief Uchida said
우치다 소장은 이렇게 말했다.
As long as I give him something
내가 그에게 뭔가를 주기만 하면
Don't hold me guilty
나를 유죄로 여기지 마세요
alright
괜찮은
I've finished explaining everything
설명을 다 마쳤어요
Man is mortal
사람은 죽는다
A worthy death
가치 있는 죽음
It's worth it too
그만한 가치도 있어요
old road
오래된 길
No matter where you are in the future
미래에는 어디에 있든 상관없어
We will all fight for the communist belief
우리는 모두 공산주의 신념을 위해 싸울 것입니다
Fight side by side
나란히 싸워라
Thank you, Mrs. Luo
고마워요, 루오 부인
Chief Uchida
우치다 소장
You are too kind
당신은 너무 친절
Actually in the future
실제로 앞으로도
There is no need to call me Mrs. Luo.
나를 루오 부인이라고 부를 필요는 없습니다.
I still like to call you Mrs. Luo
나는 아직도 당신을 루오 부인이라고 부르고 싶습니다.
fine
괜찮은
Do not worry
걱정 하지마
Original recipe
오리지널 레시피
It was taken away by Zhang Shuyun
장수윤이 빼앗아갔어
But I saw Damasao’s body
그런데 다마사오의 시체를 봤어
I knew it
알고 있었어
Uchida has set an ambush
우치다가 매복을 감행했습니다
So I can only give up
그래서 포기할 수 밖에 없어
fell into Uchida's hands
우치다의 손에 떨어졌다
Luo Guanqun deserves it
Luo Guanqun은 그럴 자격이 있습니다
I'm on my way here
난 여기로 가는 중이야
Passed by Yumo calligraphy and painting shop
유모 서예화점을 지나
But unfortunately
하지만 불행하게도
I can't kill Luo Guanqun with my own hands
내 손으로 나관춘을 죽일 수는 없어
But presumably
하지만 아마도
Is he already a bloody mess now?
그는 지금 이미 엉망진창인가요?
Chief Uchida
우치다 소장
What are you asking me to dig for?
나한테 뭘 파라고 요구하는 거야?
Manager Luo
루오 매니저
All this before my eyes
이 모든 것이 내 눈 앞에 있다
Familiar?
친숙한?
Zhao An
자오안
You also have today
너도 오늘은
I've already told Chief Uchida
우치다 소장한테는 이미 말했어
You framed Zhao An
당신은 자오안을 모함했습니다
And buried him alive here
그리고 여기에 산채로 묻어줬어요
Manager Luo
루오 매니저
your crime
당신의 범죄
It’s simply too numerous to write down.
그냥 쓰기에는 너무 많습니다.
Zhang Shuyun
장수윤
You stink
너 냄새나
Then scold
그럼 꾸짖어
Do you still want to hit me?
아직도 날 때리고 싶니?
If you dare to continue
감히 계속한다면
I actually think more highly of you
사실 난 당신을 더 높게 생각해요
Luo Guanqun
루오관쿤
From today
오늘부터
I want to follow my past
내 과거를 따라가고 싶어
Thorough farewell
철저한 이별
your past
네 과거
bid farewell
작별을 고하다
so you
그래서 당신은
You stinky woman
냄새나는 여자야
Chief Uchida
우치다 소장
I took off this skin
이 피부를 벗겨냈어
I am nothing
나는 아무것도 아니다
Please let me go
가게 해 줘
I'm not as good as a pig or a dog
나는 돼지나 개만큼 착하지 못해요
Why are you killing a person who is worse than a pig or a dog?
왜 돼지나 개보다 더 나쁜 사람을 죽이려고 합니까?
I beg you
부탁드립니다
Just let me go
그냥 날 보내줘
Shuyun
슈윤
For our sake as husband and wife
남편과 아내인 우리를 위해서
you save me
당신이 나를 구해줬어요
Break his spell and break the net
그의 주문을 깨고 그물을 부수세요
Lift the barrier of death and disaster
죽음과 재난의 장벽을 허물다
Save all injustice and suffering
모든 불의와 고통을 구하소서
Pure and bright
순수하고 밝다
Mrs. Luo
루오 부인
Manager Luo’s life and death
루오 매니저의 삶과 죽음
It's up to you
그것은 당신에게 달렸습니다
Shuyun
슈윤
Let's go
갑시다
It's too cold here
여기는 너무 추워요
Great kindness and great virtue
큰 친절과 큰 덕
Yamashita has now obtained the formula
야마시타는 이제 공식을 얻었습니다.
I haven't finished either
나도 아직 안 끝났어
The task Lao Lu gave me before his death
라오루가 죽기 전에 나에게 준 임무
I'm not willing to leave like this
이대로 떠날 마음은 없어
I think we'll have another chance
내 생각엔 우리에게 또 다른 기회가 있을 것 같아
do you have any plans
무슨 계획이라도 있어?
I will meet with my superiors in three days
나는 3일 후에 상사를 만날 것이다
The first is to hand over the copper plate
첫 번째는 동판을 건네주는 것입니다.
Two
둘
is to discuss the current situation
현재 상황을 논의하는 것입니다
And analysis
그리고 분석
Let's make a decision later
나중에 결정하자
Presumably these days
아무래도 요즘엔
Uchida will definitely treat Luo Guanqun's subordinates
우치다는 반드시 나관춘의 부하들을 대접할 것이다
Do some cleaning
청소 좀 해라
But Nariko helped us find this place.
하지만 나리코는 우리가 이곳을 찾는 데 도움을 줬어요.
In the French Concession
프랑스 조계지에서
Still very safe
여전히 매우 안전함
Let's hide here for the next few days.
앞으로 며칠간 여기에 숨어보자.
Try not to go anywhere
아무데도 가지 않으려고 해
This dealt with Zhao An and Luo Guanqun
이것은 Zhao An과 Luo Guanqun을 다루었습니다.
Unexpectedly, a money scholar appeared
뜻밖에 돈학자가 나타났다
In fact, he has been staring at us
사실 그 사람이 우리를 쳐다보고 있었거든요
morning
아침
Come to work
일하러 오세요
Those eyes hidden behind the communication room
통신실 뒤에 감춰진 그 눈빛
Like vultures circling in the sky
하늘을 맴도는 독수리처럼
Oura brothers
오우라 형제
I'm here to chat with you again
나는 당신과 다시 대화를 나누기 위해 왔습니다
The ants are all hungry
개미들이 다 배고프다
I'll give it some
내가 좀 줄게
Brush
브러시
Do not move
이동하지 않습니다
The more you move, the more you move.
더 많이 움직일수록 더 많이 움직입니다.
The ant bites harder
개미가 더 세게 물어요
now it's right
이제 맞다
Can't move
움직일 수 없다
slowly
느리게
Climb up slowly
천천히 올라가요
even though
~ 일지라도
you say
당신은 말한다
You told me everything you know
당신은 당신이 알고 있는 모든 것을 나에게 말했어요
But just in case
하지만 혹시라도
Is there anything else you haven't told me?
나한테 아직 말하지 않은 게 또 있나요?
What about me?
나는 어때?
No advantages
장점 없음
Just meticulous
그냥 꼼꼼함
Who goes to work at what time?
누가 몇시에 출근하나요?
What time do you get off work?
몇시에 퇴근해요?
What letters did you receive?
어떤 편지를 받았나요?
What visitors did we receive?
우리는 어떤 방문자를 받았습니까?
I remember everything clearly
나는 모든 것을 선명하게 기억한다
Brush a little more Brush a little more
조금 더 빗어주세요 조금 더 빗어주세요
After investigation
조사 후
The batch of cotton yarn that framed Zhao An
조안(趙靖)을 감싼 면사 묶음
Luo Guanqun also hoarded purchases many times in Shanghai
Luo Guanqun도 상하이에서 여러 번 구매를 축적했습니다.
cotton
면
Scarce items such as Western medicine
양약 등 희소품
Without access to the Gendarmerie Headquarters
헌병대 본부 접근 불가
permitted
허용됨
Privately transported to the Guotou District of northern Zhejiang
저장성 북부 궈터우구로 개인 수송
Some are traded for tung oil wood, etc.
일부는 퉁 오일 우드 등으로 거래됩니다.
Then transport it back to Hangzhou and Sunan area for resale.
그런 다음 재판매를 위해 항저우와 순안 지역으로 다시 운송하십시오.
Some are direct cash transactions
일부는 직접 현금거래
Huge amount
엄청난 양
jaw-dropping
입이 쩍 벌어지는
These are the interrogation records and ledgers
심문기록과 장부입니다
Taihe Trading Company is now an empty shelf.
Taihe Trading Company는 이제 빈 선반입니다.
Someone needs to step forward immediately
누군가는 당장 나서야 한다
Yes Yes
예 예
correct
옳은
Just now you mentioned that in the Chronicles of the Kingdoms of the Eastern Zhou Dynasty
방금 당신은 『동주나라실록』에서 이런 말을 했습니다.
What's the name of that janitor?
그 관리인 이름이 뭐죠?
Hou Ying
허우 잉
Later it was him
나중에는 그 사람이었어
He offered Lord Xinling a plan to steal the talisman to save Zhao.
그는 Xinling 경에게 Zhao를 구하기 위해 부적을 훔칠 계획을 제안했습니다.
It seems
것 같다
Do you want to be a person like Hou Ying?
허우잉 같은 사람이 되고 싶나요?
Don't dare
감히 하지 마세요
Although you have made a great contribution this time
이번에는 큰 공헌을 했지만
But because of this
하지만 이것 때문에
Help you become a business manager
당신이 비즈니스 매니저가 될 수 있도록 도와주세요
I'm afraid it's still hard to convince the public.
아직은 대중을 설득하기가 어려운 것 같아요.
Yes Yes
예 예
but
하지만
I hope sir will give me a chance
선생님께서 저에게 기회를 주셨으면 좋겠습니다.
Continue to serve the Empire of Japan
계속해서 일본제국에 봉사하라
what else can you do
너는 어떤 다른 일을 할 수 있니
I just heard the commander say
방금 지휘관이 하는 말을 들었어
Mr. Yamashita’s great ambitions
야마시타 씨의 큰 야망
Only the edge coin copper plate is missing
엣지 코인 동판만 빠졌네요
What a pity
정말 안타깝네요
when we know
우리가 알 때
Wang Dapu’s true identity later
왕다푸의 정체는 나중에 밝혀진다
He has escaped from prison
그는 감옥에서 탈출했다
In addition, I also heard that our firm
게다가 우리 회사에서도 들었어.
There have been two lurkers hidden all this time
그동안 숨어 있던 두 명의 러커가 있었습니다.
The Four of Clubs of the Communist Party of China and the Five of Hearts of the Military Command
중국 공산당 4대 클럽과 군 사령부 5심
yes
예
The people inside the commercial bank should be arrested now.
당장 상업은행 내부 사람들을 체포해야 합니다.
Die, die
그것들, 그것들
Those who should run also ran away.
도망쳐야 할 자도 도망쳤다.
The only thing is this plum blossom and heart
이 매화와 하트뿐이야
Who is it?
누구입니까?
still a mystery
아직도 미스터리
According to the information we have received before
이전에 받은 정보에 따르면
their purpose
그들의 목적
It should be Mr. Yamashita
야마시타 씨일 겁니다
A secret plan that goes all out
총력을 기울이는 비밀 계획
If these two people cannot be caught in one day
이 두 사람을 하루만에 잡을 수 없다면
Mr. Yamashita still has trouble sleeping and eating.
야마시타 씨는 아직도 잠을 자고 먹는 데 어려움을 겪고 있습니다.
Secretary
비서
I
나
I, Qian Chengyi, would like to ask for your order
저 Qian Chengyi가 귀하의 주문을 요청하고 싶습니다.
The first is to win the copper plate of the border coin
첫 번째는 국경 동전의 동판을 획득하는 것입니다.
The second is to eradicate clubs, four hearts and five hearts.
두 번째는 클럽, 4심, 5심 근절입니다.
you
너
See you tomorrow
내일 봐요
I have something important to say to Mr. Yamashita
야마시타 씨에게 중요한 할 말이 있어요
you wait here
여기서 기다리세요
Why are you back again?
왜 다시 돌아왔나요?
Look at my brain
내 뇌를 좀 봐
I forgot something
잊어버린 게 있어요
Aoyama-kun
아오야마 군
I suddenly remembered
문득 생각났어요
I have a preparatory document for epidemic prevention
전염병 예방을 위한 준비서류가 있습니다
Forgot to file
제출하는 것을 잊어버렸습니다
I have to go back again
다시 돌아가야 해
Now every month we
이제 우리는 매달
Counterfeit fiat currency printed and issued
위조 법정화폐 인쇄 및 발행
All reached more than five million
모두 500만 돌파
Legal currency issued by the Chongqing government last year
지난해 충칭시 정부가 발행한 법정 화폐
at 400 million yuan
400만원에
Legal currency flowing into Kuomintang-controlled areas through the Sugi Plan
Sugi Plan을 통해 국민당 통제 지역으로 유입되는 법정 화폐
has reached 5% of the total circulation rate
전체 유통량의 5%에 도달했습니다.
Inflation in Kuomintang-controlled areas
국민당 통제 지역의 인플레이션
Therefore, it is greatly accelerated
그러므로 속도가 많이 빨라진다.
Not only that
뿐만 아니라
We are still in Chongqing, Hunan, Hubei and Guangxi
우리는 아직 충칭, 후난, 후베이, 광시에 있습니다.
Wait for multiple unoccupied areas
여러 개의 비어 있는 영역을 기다립니다.
Established a bank
은행 설립
through bank
은행을 통해
Our counterfeit fiat currency flows to the market
우리의 위조 화폐가 시장으로 유입됩니다
At the same time we are in Chongqing
동시에 우리는 충칭에 있습니다
Two companies, Yusheng and Minxing, were also established.
Yusheng과 Minxing이라는 두 회사도 설립되었습니다.
Leverage our counterfeit fiat currency
위조 법정화폐 활용
Purchased a large amount of strategic supplies
전략물자 대량 구매
Now
지금
I'm more confident
좀 더 자신감이 생겼어요
Advancing the cedar plan
삼나무 계획 추진
Thanks
감사해요
Mr. Qingshan is wrong
Qingshan 씨가 틀렸어요
What about epidemic prevention?
전염병 예방은 어떻습니까?
In Library No. 3
3번 도서관 내
This is number two
이게 2번째야
What a trouble
정말 문제다
Thanks for your hard work
당신의 노고에 감사드립니다
Communist Party
공산당
Established a financial system for overall planning and expenditure
전반적인 기획 및 지출을 위한 재정시스템 구축
Many miscellaneous taxes were abolished
각종 각종 세금이 폐지되었습니다.
The border area is developing very rapidly
국경 지역은 매우 빠르게 발전하고 있습니다.
who are you
누구세요
I came here with Chief Uchida
우치다 과장님과 함께 왔습니다
Is there a problem
문제가 있습니까
I want to ask
나는 묻고 싶다
Is there anyone in Library No. 3?
3번 도서관에 사람이 있나요?
Yes, I have
네, 있어요
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
I was in Library No. 3 just now
나 지금 3번 도서관에 있었어
There seems to be some strange sound coming from
뭔가 이상한 소리가 들리는 것 같아
What a strange sound
정말 이상한 소리네요
Just a bang
그냥 쾅
I don't know what happened either
나도 무슨 일이 일어났는지 모르겠어
Maybe the file box fell on the floor?
어쩌면 파일 상자가 바닥에 떨어진 걸까요?
correct
옳은
I also heard the sound of swish, swish, swish
휙, 휙, 휙 하는 소리도 들었어
It seems like tearing paper
종이를 찢는 것 같아
That's right
좋아요
Absolutely not
절대적으로하지
I gonna go see
보러 갈게
Chongqing Government
충칭 정부
Already now
이미 지금
Intensified the comprehensive blockade of border areas
국경지역 전면 봉쇄 강화
It is enough to explain that Chongqing
충칭에 대해 설명하는 것만으로도 충분합니다.
Already caused panic in Chongqing
이미 충칭에서는 패닉을 일으켰습니다.
even so
비록 그렇다 하더라도
Still no fatal blow
아직 치명타는 없어
so
그래서
The second phase of the Sugi plan
삼기계획의 두 번째 단계
It is to disrupt and destroy the economy of the border areas
국경지역의 경제를 교란하고 파괴하는 것이다.
as the focus
초점으로
cedar plan
삼나무 계획
The location of the second stage of advancement
2단계 발전의 위치
Just put it in the new place
그냥 새로운 곳에 넣어두세요
Who?
WHO?
Lu Fangfang
루팡팡
are you in there
너 거기 있어?
yes
예
I am here
나는 여기 있다
What's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
you open the door
당신은 문을 연다
My hands are full of documents
내 손에는 서류가 가득해요
Please wait a moment
잠시만 기다려주세요
Why can't the door open?
왜 문이 열리지 않나요?
Maybe it's stuck
어쩌면 붙어있을지도 몰라
Hold on
기다리다
Qian Xiucai
치안 슈카이
Are you OK
괜찮으세요
it's okay no problem
괜찮아 문제 없어
Aoyama-kun
아오야마 군
What the hell is going on?
도대체 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
Did you tear out any documents?
서류를 찢으셨나요?
Tear documents
문서 찢기
how could it be possible
어떻게 그게 가능하겠어?
I do not have it
제가 그건 없어요
If you doubt me
나를 의심한다면
You can check every document here
여기에서 모든 문서를 확인할 수 있습니다
Check to see if there are any signs of tearing
찢어진 흔적이 있는지 확인하세요.
You can also search me
당신도 나를 검색할 수 있습니다
Come
오다
I understand the rules of the Military Police Headquarters.
나는 헌병 본부의 규칙을 이해합니다.
Open
열려 있는
Have it
그것을 가지고
Did you hear clearly?
분명히 들었나요?
I
나
Qian Chengyi
첸 청이
I'm here
나는 여기 있다
what are you doing there
너 거기서 뭐해
Come in
올
cedar plan
삼나무 계획
The location of the second stage of advancement
2단계 발전의 위치
Just put it in the new place
그냥 새로운 곳에 넣어두세요
new ground
새로운 땅
Could it be a place name?
지명일까요?
Come
오다
Secretary
비서
Slower
느리게
It's you
당신이에요
why follow me
왜 나를 따라와?
Captain Liu is dead
류 선장은 죽었다
What
무엇
It was Chen Jiaping who killed Captain Liu
Liu 선장을 죽인 사람은 Chen Jiaping이었습니다.
It was you who killed Captain Liu
류 선장을 죽인 건 너였어
impossible
불가능한
Chen Jiaping told me that Captain Liu saved him
Chen Jiaping은 Liu 선장이 그를 구했다고 말했습니다.
He also told him a secret passage to avoid arrest.
체포를 피하기 위한 비밀 통로도 알려줬다.
Captain Liu wants to save you
Liu 선장은 당신을 구하고 싶어합니다
He didn't want to save Chen Jiaping at all
그는 Chen Jiaping을 전혀 구하고 싶지 않았습니다.
He just wants to get the copper plate back
그는 단지 동판을 되찾고 싶을 뿐이에요
Chen Jiaping killed him
천자핑이 죽였어
I do not believe
난 믿지 않아
you are too naive
당신은 너무 순진해요
How is it possible for Captain Liu?
Liu 선장은 어떻게 가능합니까?
Go help a communist party
가서 공산당을 도와주세요
You were deceived by Chen Jiaping
당신은 Chen Jiaping에게 속았습니다
How did you know
어떻게 알았어?
I was not far from Captain Liu at that time
그 당시 나는 Liu 선장과 멀지 않았습니다.
It was Chen Jiaping who shot him
그를 쏜 사람은 Chen Jiaping이었습니다.
I can see clearly
나는 분명히 볼 수 있다
But I was too scared then
근데 그때는 너무 무서웠어
Didn't dare to step forward
감히 나서지 못했다.
There is no way to save Captain Liu
류 선장을 구할 방법은 없습니다
impossible
불가능한
Jia Ping is not such a person
Jia Ping은 그런 사람이 아닙니다
What is impossible
불가능한 것은 무엇입니까?
I saw it with my own eyes
나는 그것을 내 눈으로 보았다.
Director Jiang is right
장 감독 말이 맞다
You have been turned red
당신은 빨갛게 변했습니다
Been brainwashed
세뇌당했어
Captain Liu
리우 선장
where is the body
시체는 어디에 있나요?
Although you are very strict
당신은 매우 엄격하지만
There is something bright in your heart
당신의 마음에는 밝은 것이 있습니다
i can feel it
느낄 수있어
shiny things
반짝이는 것들
actually
실제로
I also have something to tell you
나도 너한테 할 말이 있어
But today is not the right time
하지만 오늘은 때가 아니야
next time
다음번
Now you believe it
이제 당신은 그것을 믿나요?
sorry
죄송합니다
Captain Liu
리우 선장
Why have you been gone so long?
왜 그렇게 오랫동안 떠나 있었나요?
I'm not thinking about you. Do you like to eat pan-fried buns?
나는 당신에 대해 생각하지 않습니다. 팬에 튀긴 빵을 좋아하시나요?
I went to several houses
여러 집에 가봤는데
You haven't encountered anything, right?
당신은 아무 일도 겪지 않았죠?
No
아니요
Something on my mind
뭔가 생각나는 게 있어
Just a little worried
그냥 좀 걱정돼
I don’t know what to do next
다음에 무엇을 해야할지 모르겠어요
Do you remember what I told you?
내가 말한 것을 기억하나요?
Is this the last thing I said to Lao Lu?
이것이 내가 라오루에게 마지막으로 한 말인가요?
We fight side by side
우리는 나란히 싸운다
As long as we fight side by side
우리가 나란히 싸우는 한
can overcome all difficulties
모든 어려움을 이겨낼 수 있다
fight side by side
나란히 싸우다
Lu Fangfang
루팡팡
How come there is a monthly pass card for the Bund Park?
Bund Park에 월간 패스 카드가 있는 이유는 무엇입니까?
Will it be the Bund Park?
Bund Park가 될까요?
is a fixed joint location
고정된 관절 위치입니다.
Section Chief Chen
첸 과장
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Qian Xiucai
치안 슈카이
That
저것
Where is the fountain?
분수는 어디에 있나요?
Is this a car wash that costs nothing and is clean?
이게 돈도 안 들고 깨끗한 세차장인가요?
Could it be
그럴 수 있을까?
Lu Fangfang
루팡팡
The contact person at the Bund Park is
Bund Park의 담당자는 다음과 같습니다.
Four of Plum Blossoms by Chen Jiaping
천가평(陳嘉平)의 네 개의 매화(梅梅)
Sir, take a look
선생님, 좀 보세요
Which one do you like?
당신은 어느 것을 좋아합니까?
This is the letter Captain Liu wrote to you
이것은 류 선장이 당신에게 쓴 편지입니다
actually
실제로
Captain Liu
리우 선장
I've noticed the change in your mentality a long time ago
오래 전부터 너의 사고방식의 변화를 알아차렸어
It's just that he's too soft-hearted towards you
그 사람이 너한테 너무 마음이 여린 것뿐이야
Otherwise, we wouldn’t have ended up like this today.
그렇지 않았다면 우리는 오늘 이렇게 되지 않았을 것이다.
Five of Hearts Commissioner
파이브 오브 하트 위원
I've noticed recently that your faith is wavering
나는 최근에 당신의 믿음이 흔들리고 있다는 것을 깨달았습니다.
Annihilation of ideals
이상의 소멸
Makes me feel anxious and frightened
나를 불안하고 두렵게 만든다.
gather will
의지를 모으다
Defend the leader’s purpose
리더의 목적을 옹호하라
Must be engraved in the heart
마음에 새겨야 할
formulated by the Fifth Plenary Session of the Kuomintang Central Committee
국민당 중앙위원회 제5차 전원회의에서 제정
The policy of dissolving communism, preventing communism, limiting communism and opposing communism
공산주의를 해체하고, 공산주의를 방지하고, 공산주의를 제한하고, 공산주의를 반대하는 정책
More importantly, we must resolutely implement
더 중요한 것은 우리가 이를 단호하게 실행해야 한다는 것입니다.
Never be deceived by the CCP’s words
절대로 중국 공산당의 말에 속지 마십시오
There must be no more disobedient behavior
더 이상 불순종한 행위는 없어야 합니다
if not
그렇지 않다면
Jiangsu and Zhejiang Action Committee
장쑤성 및 저장성 행동위원회
All great achievements will be in vain
모든 위대한 성취는 헛될 것이다
Remember remember
기억해 기억해
How about it
어때요?
Now for what you did before
이제 이전에 했던 일에 대해
Have you repented?
회개하셨나요?
Think about it now
지금 생각해 보세요
how simple you are
당신은 얼마나 단순합니까?
How childish
얼마나 유치한가
I tell you
나는 당신에게 말한다
in this world
이 세상에서
Not at all
별말씀을요
As noble a person as you imagine
당신이 상상하는 만큼 고귀한 사람
noble doctrine
고귀한 교리
we are not
우리는하지 않습니다
He is not even a communist
그 사람은 공산주의자도 아니다.
Everyone is doing it for their own selfish interests
다들 자기 이익을 위해 그러는거임
You fight for it
당신은 그것을 위해 싸운다
play hard
열심히 놀다
Our people have found it
우리 국민이 찾았어요
Contact information between Chen Jiaping and his superiors
Chen Jiaping과 그의 상사 사이의 연락처 정보
Bring back the copper plate
동판을 돌려주세요
give it to me
그걸 나에게주세요
Kill Chen Jiaping
천자핑(Chen Jiaping)을 죽여라
Revenge for Liu Wuchang
유무창에 대한 복수
what do I do
나는 무엇을 해야 하는가
you know what to do
넌 뭘해야 할 지 알 잖아
Is there any problem with killing Chen Jiaping?
Chen Jiaping을 죽이는 데 문제가 있습니까?
old road
오래된 길
Thank you
감사합니다
Lu Fangfang
루팡팡
Why did you come?
왜 왔나요?
what are you doing
뭐하세요
do not move
이동하지 않습니다
I am a parrot
나는 앵무새입니다
hug me
안아줘
This is an order
이것은 명령이다
Don't turn around
돌아서지 마세요
At my nine o'clock position
내 9시 위치에서
There's a sniper targeting you
당신을 노리는 저격수가 있습니다
The connector target has appeared
커넥터 대상이 나타났습니다.
can shoot
쏠 수 있다
etc.
등.
That woman doesn't look like she's here to hook up.
그 여자는 연애하려고 온 것 같지 않아요.
Why didn't you evacuate when you knew there was danger?
위험하다는 걸 알면서도 왜 대피하지 않았나요?